Hello Hello
Here comes some more about the subject
verbal interaction
to get better at talking, on talking
to converse
In a new language, such as Swedish
and how to train on it
and what is good to think about
and
this may really be the most
to throw things into the conversation
to open the call
with interesting things as it is possible for the other to
give response to, to react to
to reflect
but also to spin on
As I talked (about) in the last video
Because if you just say
the most mundane phrases
If you just ask "How are you?"
and "How's the situation?"
and
"How's your family?"
and then there will be a longer call
and someone else is interested in music
and a third is interested in talking about the job and so on
It is based on you throw in something
you give a small hook that the other can
spin on / build on
yeah so to, think a little bit about it
were you around you
in your life?
What are you doing?
What are you interested in?
What do you think about?
What are you planning in the future?